freevectors.net 2015-05-22

# Free Vector Art & Graphics :: Privacy Policy

[FreeVectors.net](http://www.freevectors.net/) is committed to providing you with a safe online environment for exchanging graphic resources. As with any website, by visiting our site and engaging in certain activities, we may collect certain identifying information which can and will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. FreeVectors.net may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 2/7/14. 

FreeVectors.net may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 2/7/14. 

As a visitor to the Site, you can participate in many activities without providing any Personal Information.

When choosing to participate in select activities, such as completing an online form or submitting artwork to FreeVectors.net, you may be asked to provide information such as your name and email address. This information is only gathered for the use of FreeVectors.net and will not be redistributed to any third-party companies. 

As with any website, we may also gather and store non-personal information obtained through technological resources that may be transparent to the end user through the use of cookies. For further explanation about cookies, see the section “How we use cookies”. 

We gather information about your website activity only with the intent of improving and customizing your user experience while on our site. We’re committed to protecting your privacy, so we do not sell, rent or share your personal information to or with third parties in any way other than as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable electronic and managerial procedures to secure the information we collect online.

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added, and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However, many activities on our site require the use of cookies so disabling cookies may negatively impact your user experience on our site.

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time. Simply [contact us](http://www.freevectors.net/contact) and we will remove your personal information from our system.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. 

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please [contact us](http://www.freevectors.net/contact) as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

We do not intend to solicit or collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18 without parental consent. If you are under 18, do not enter information on this site or engage our services. If you believe a child of yours under the age of 18 has entered Personal Information please [contact us](http://www.freevectors.net/contact) immediately to have the data removed.
